[
    {
        "question": "This word is a shrub with tubular flowers!",
        "answer": "Fuchsia"
    },

    {
        "question": "This is a soft, gentle breeze.",
        "answer": "Zephyr"
    },

    {
        "question": "This word means to consent or to allow.",
        "answer": "Acquiesce"
    },

    {
        "question": "Frogs, toads, and salamanders are all examples of this word!",
        "answer": "Amphibian"
    },

    {
        "question": "Synonyms of this word are certainly, surely, unquestionable, and without doubt!",
        "answer": "Definitely"
    },

    {
        "question": "This word comes from the Malay and Indonesian words for “person” and “forest”!",
        "answer": "Orangutan"
    },

    {
        "question": "This word means to accuse someone of wrongdoing!",
        "answer": "Indict"
    },

    {
        "question": "Some people claim to have none of this when it comes to dancing.",
        "answer": "Rhythm"
    },

    {
        "question": "This word comes from two French words, couvrir, which means “to cover” and chef, which means “head.”",
        "answer": "Handkerchief"
    },

    {
        "question": "This word, meaning a deep, immeasurable space!",
        "answer": "Abyss"
    },

    {
        "question": "This creature is the largest reptile in North America.",
        "answer": "Alligator"
    },

    {
        "question": "You can eat this dish for breakfast.",
        "answer": "Flapjack"
    },

    {
        "question": "You can bring this thing back from your trip.",
        "answer": "Memento"
    },

    {
        "question": "The antelope of Eastern and Southern Africa.",
        "answer": "Wildebeest"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the name of the technology fairy in the animated series Winx?",
        "answer": "Tecna"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the name of the technology fairyThe main female character of Victor Hugo's work “Notre Dame Cathedral”.",
        "answer": "Esmeralda"
    },

    {
        "question": "The name of the main male character in Jane Austen's novel “Pride and Prejudice.”",
        "answer": "Fitzwilliam"
    },

    {
        "question": "The name of the first programmer.",
        "answer": "Ada"
    },

    {
        "question": "The scalar product of two nonzero vectors is zero if and only if these vectors are ...",
        "answer": "Perpendicular"
    }
]